Martha Radosevich Posters ARC.0060
Library and Archives
Martha Radosevich Posters
1980-1984, undated
ARC.0060
Library and Archives
4.0 Linear feet (1 shared flat file drawer)
The Martha Radosevich Posters span the years 1980 to 1984. The collection consists of 32 concert posters for various performers, bands, and venues in the Southern California area. The majority of the posters were printed by the Colby Poster Printing Company in Los Angeles, California. Artists and bands documented in the collection include James Brown, Ray Charles, Jimmy Cliff, The Cramps, Echo and the Bunnymen, John Lee Hooker, Jerry Garcia Band, B.B. King, Wilson Pickett, The Police, R.E.M., Romeo Void, Sex Pistols, Stevie Ray Vaughan, and Warren Zevon. Venues include the Beverly Theatre, Forum, Greek Theatre, Hollywood Palladium, Hollywood Park, and Roxy Theatre. The collection provides a sampling of concert posters that would have been posted in the Southern California area in the early- to mid-1980s. Seen in a broader context, the collection provides insights to how performers and venues promoted their shows from in the early 1980s and the performers from that era. The Martha Radosevich Posters are arranged chronologically.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights statement on the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. Consult the Library and Archives in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Custodial History
The Martha Radosevich Posters were received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum as a gift from Radosevich on September 25, 2009.
Babylon Warriors (Musical group); Berlin (Musical group); Blades (Musical group); Bland, Bobby; Blasters (Musical group); Brown, James, 1933-2006; Burnett, T-Bone; Charles, Ray, 1930-2004; Cliff, Jimmy; Cramps (Musical group); Difford and Tilbrook; Dixon, Willie, 1915-1992; Echo and the Bunnymen; Fixx (Musical group); Fleshtones (Musical group); Gaye, Marvin; Greek Theatre Association (Los Angeles, Calif.); Green, Al, 1946-; Guy, Buddy; Hooker, John Lee; James, Etta, 1938-2012; James, Rick, 1948-2004; Jerry Garcia Band; Johansen, David, 1950-; King, Albert, 1923-1992; King, B.B.; Little Milton; Naughty Sweeties (Musical group); Neville Brothers; Pickett, Wilson; Police (Musical group); Psychedelic Furs (Musical group); R.E.M. (Musical group); Reeves, Martha; Romeo Void (Musical group); Sex Pistols (Musical group); Sparks (Musical group); Taj Mahal (Musician); Taylor, Koko; Thompson Twins (Musical group); Toots and the Maytals (Musical group); Tosh, Peter; Turner, Joe, 1911-1985; Vaughan, Stevie Ray.; Walker, Jr.; Wells, Junior, 1934-1998; Wild Tchoupitoulas (Musical group); Witherspoon, Jimmy; Zevon, Warren; Posters; Rock concerts; Rock music; Rock music--Posters
- Sex Pistols in D.O.A., 1980 June 12-1980 June 18; 22" x 13.75" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 1)
- Toots and the Maytals, 1981 March 2; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 2)
- Blades, 1981 May 26; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 3)
- Romeo Void, The Brat, 1981 August 18; 17" x 11" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 4)
- Babylon Warriors, Martha Reeves, Hunt Sales and Big 9, Uprising, 1981 October 2; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 5)
  Condition
  Placed in mylar.
- Naughty Sweeties, Unit III with Venus, 1982 February 11; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 6)
- King, B.B., 1982 April 10; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 7)
- Charles, Ray, with Ray Charles Orchestra and the Raeletts, 1982 April 23; 21.75" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 8)
- Brown, James, Junior Walker, WIlson Pickett, 1982 June 21-1982 July 1; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 9)
- Johansen, David, 1982 June 28-1982 June 30; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 10)
- Benson, George, 1982 July 6-1982 July 10; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 11)
- James, Rick, Ray Parker Jr., 1982 August 20-1982 August 21; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 12)
- 3rd Annual Long Beach Blues Festival: Taj Mahal, Little Milton, Ester Phillips, The Johnny Otis Show, Gatemouth Brown, 1982 September 19; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 13)
- Jerry Garcia Band, Sparks, The Cramps, Warren Zevon, 1982 October 28-1982 October 31; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 14)
- Burnett, T-Bone, 1982 November 2; 22" x 13.75" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 15)
- Neville Brothers, Wild Tchoupitoulas, Peter Tosh, 1982 November 2-1982 November 8; 28" x 16" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 16)
- Gaye, Marvin, 1983 August 14; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 17)
- The Blasters, Wailin' Walker and the House Rockers, 1983 August 18; 16.75" x 11" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 18)
- Klemmer, John, James Brown, B.B. King, 1983 August 19-1983 August 20; 28" x 14.5" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 19)
- Vaughan, Stevie Ray, 1983 August 22; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 20)
- Tosh, Peter, 1983 August 22-1983 August 23; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 21)
- Green, Al, 1983 August 24; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 22)
- The Police, Berlin, The Fixx, Thompson Twins, 1983 September 6; 21.75" x 13.75" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 23)
- 4th Annual Long Beach Blues Festival: Bobby Blue Bland, Albert King, Willie Dixon, Johnny Copeland, Koko Taylor, Clifton Chenier, Jimmy McCracklin, Sonny Rhodes, Freddie Roulette, 1983 September 18; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 24-25)
- Difford and Tilbrook, 1984 August 17-1984 August 18; 26" x 15" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 26)
- Psychedelic Furs, The Call, 1984 August 20; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 27)
- R.E.M., The Swimming Pool Q's, 1984 September 6; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 28)
- Echo and the Bunnymen, The Fleshtones, 1984 September 9; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 29)
- 5th Annual Long Beach Blues Festival: B.B. King, John Lee Hooker, Etta James, Denise LaSalle, Big Joe Turner, James Cotton, Pee Wee Crayton, Son Seals, Buddy Guy and Junior Wells, Jimmy Witherspoon, Brownie McGhee, 1984 September 15-1984 September 16; 22" x 14" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 30)
- Cliff, Jimmy, August 19; 22" x 15.25" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 31)
- Rock on Films, December 31-January 17; 21.75" x15" (Drawer-folder FF.1.2-6, Object 32)